{
  "number" : 10,
  "0": {
    "problem": "55 + 5 - (45 + 5)",
    "answer": 10
  },
  "1": {
    "problem": "4 * (3 + 4)",
    "answer": 28
  },
  "2": {
    "problem": "9 - (30 / 5)",
    "answer": 3
  },
  "3": {
    "problem": "(17 - 3) + (7 - 5)",
    "answer": 16
  },
  "4": {
    "problem": "(13 - 4) / 3",
    "answer": 3
  },
  "5": {
    "problem": "45 / 5 - 4",
    "answer": 5
  },
  "6": {
    "problem": "6 * 7 - 2",
    "answer": 40
  },
  "7": {
    "problem": "90 - 40 + 5 - (5 - 4)",
    "answer": 54
  },
  "8": {
    "problem": "32 - 5 + 3",
    "answer": 30
  },
  "9": {
    "problem": "(76 + 4) / 4",
    "answer": 20
  }
}